

# **MOHAMED DAWAH**

#### **CONTACT INFO**

- **\** +48538278499
- M.dawah94@gmail.com
- Y Katowice. Poland
- My Website

modawah.github.io/portofilio

#### **EDUCATION**

bachelor degree of social work Delta university

#### 2018-2019

web development deploma udacity

## LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

polish

# **PROFILE**

Highly accurate data entry with 2 years experience,

high Typing Speed with zero errors.

Maintained 99% accuracy in two fast-paced data entry positions. Used MS Office daily, including Outlook and Excel.

Devised several MS Excel macros to automate repetitive tasks. Increased efficiency by 33%.

Computer and technical skills (including software knowledge).

Organisational and time management abilities.

Administrative skills.

Communication (written and verbal).

also management skills due my 2 years of managing Grocery Store.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2016-2018 **SELLER** 

GROCERY STORE serving customers, ordering and restocking the

products

2018-2020 **DATA ENTRY** 

IREM.S.P.A

office works (excel, word and powerpoint). (ZOHR GAS FIELD PROJECT) daily productivity reports.

archiving and files managemnt.

using company server's software to store data.

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

MS OFFICE HTML **EXCEL** CSS WORD **JAVASCRIPT POWERPOINT BOOTSTRAP** 

## **INTEREST**

sport </>coding reading **a**gaming